[
{"type":"header","version":"5.1.1","comment":"Export to JSON plugin for PHPMyAdmin"},
{"type":"database","name":"wcrmkt"},
{"type":"table","name":"bible_quizzes","database":"wcrmkt","data":
[
{"id":"3","question":"During the time of Elisha's sickness what did he tell Joash to take hold of","optn1":"Seventeen fish","optn2":"Bow and arrows","optn3":"The writings of King David","optn4":"Cup of milk","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 01:43:30","updated_at":"2022-10-19 01:43:30"},
{"id":"4","question":"What happened to the Moabite who was buried in the grave of Elisha?","optn1":"Swallowed up by the earth","optn2":"Turned to stone","optn3":"Vanished","optn4":"Resurrected","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 01:45:47","updated_at":"2022-10-19 01:45:47"},
{"id":"5","question":"Which ruler wanted the baby Jesus killed?","optn1":"Tiberius","optn2":"Philip","optn3":"Herod","optn4":"Augustus","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 01:52:04","updated_at":"2022-10-19 01:52:04"},
{"id":"6","question":"What does Jesus say that the meek shall inherit?","optn1":"Everlasting life","optn2":"The Treasure of Heaven","optn3":"The earth","optn4":"The Throne of God","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 01:57:13","updated_at":"2022-10-19 01:57:13"},
{"id":"7","question":"What was Jesus talking about when he said you can't make one hair on your head black or white?","optn1":"Resurrection","optn2":"Forgiveness","optn3":"Oaths","optn4":"Fasting","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 01:59:17","updated_at":"2022-10-19 01:59:17"},
{"id":"8","question":"How should we practise charitable works, prayers and fasting?","optn1":"With thanksgiving","optn2":"Openly","optn3":"Quietly","optn4":"In secret","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:00:27","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:00:27"},
{"id":"9","question":"Where was Matthew sitting when Jesus called him?","optn1":"In a fishing boat","optn2":"By a well","optn3":"In a tax booth","optn4":"On a donkey","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:01:56","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:01:56"},
{"id":"10","question":"Which disciple was told to catch a fish that would hold a coin in its mouth?","optn1":"Philip","optn2":"Peter","optn3":"Andrew","optn4":"James","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:04:04","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:04:04"},
{"id":"11","question":"which book comes after Job?","optn1":"Ezra","optn2":"Psalms","optn3":"Proverbs","optn4":"Esther","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:05:36","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:05:36"},
{"id":"12","question":"which book comes after Hebrews?","optn1":"Revelation","optn2":"1 Peter","optn3":"Philemon","optn4":"James","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:07:51","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:07:51"},
{"id":"13","question":"which is  the 10th book in Bible?","optn1":"Ruth","optn2":"1 Kings","optn3":"2 Samuel","optn4":"Judges","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:11:09","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:11:09"},
{"id":"14","question":"Which king was killed by two of his sons as he was worshipping?","optn1":"Cyrus","optn2":"Shalmaneser","optn3":"Sennacherib","optn4":"Zedekiah","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:13:43","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:13:43"},
{"id":"15","question":"Which king saw the writing on the wall?","optn1":"Benhadad","optn2":"Herod Antipas","optn3":"Belshazzar","optn4":"Nebuchadnezzar","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:15:20","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:15:20"},
{"id":"16","question":"Which king gave Abram bread and wine?","optn1":"Melchizedek","optn2":"Piram","optn3":"Abimelech","optn4":"Hoshea","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:17:23","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:17:23"},
{"id":"17","question":"Which king had Daniel thrown into the lion's den?","optn1":"Darius","optn2":"Eglon","optn3":"Nebuchadnezzar","optn4":"Og","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:19:54","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:19:54"},
{"id":"18","question":"What did God do on the 7th day of creation?","optn1":"Created man","optn2":"Created light","optn3":"Created Eve","optn4":"Rested","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:29:07","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:29:07"},
{"id":"19","question":"What did God place with the cherubim to guard the Tree of Life?","optn1":"Four-headed beast","optn2":"Flaming sword","optn3":"Mighty lion","optn4":"River of sulphur","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:30:21","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:30:21"},
{"id":"20","question":"What was the name of the place where God confused the language of all the people?","optn1":"Babylon","optn2":"Bethel","optn3":"Babel","optn4":"Beersheba","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:32:05","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:32:05"},
{"id":"21","question":"What was the name of Ishmael's mother?","optn1":"Sarai","optn2":"Milcah","optn3":"Hagar","optn4":"Zilpah","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:33:23","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:33:23"},
{"id":"22","question":"What did Abraham purchase from the Hittites for 400 shekels of silver?","optn1":"Lake","optn2":"City","optn3":"House","optn4":"Field","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:35:53","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:35:53"},
{"id":"23","question":"Why did Jacob flee to live with Laban?","optn1":"Esau wanted to kill him","optn2":"He had sinned against God","optn3":"He had stolen from his father","optn4":"Abimelech wanted his wife","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:38:50","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:38:50"},
{"id":"24","question":"What was the name of Abraham's second wife?","optn1":"Keturah","optn2":"Shua","optn3":"Anah","optn4":"Timna","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:40:25","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:40:25"},
{"id":"25","question":"Which two of Jacob's sons took revenge on Shechem?","optn1":"Reuben and Benjamin","optn2":"Asher and Dan","optn3":"Simeon and Levi","optn4":"Naphtali and Issachar","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:42:38","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:42:38"},
{"id":"26","question":"How old was Isaac when he died?","optn1":"70","optn2":"147","optn3":"120","optn4":"180","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:43:40","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:43:40"},
{"id":"27","question":"Who bought Joseph as his slave from the Ishmaelites?","optn1":"Potiphar","optn2":"Phicol","optn3":"Cyrus","optn4":"Pharaoh","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:45:14","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:45:14"},
{"id":"28","question":"What did Joseph do for Pharaoh that got him promoted to second in command over Egypt?","optn1":"Rescued his daughter","optn2":"Uncovered a plot to murder Pharaoh","optn3":"Interpreted dreams","optn4":"Healed his sickness","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:48:11","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:48:11"},
{"id":"29","question":"In what area of Egypt did Jacob and his family settle?","optn1":"Upper Egypt","optn2":"El-Badari","optn3":"Pathros","optn4":"Goshen","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:50:20","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:50:20"},
{"id":"30","question":"Who trusted God and made the journey from Babylon to Jerusalem without protection from soldiers?","optn1":"Ahaziah","optn2":"Ezra","optn3":"Haggai","optn4":"Mordeca","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:53:55","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:53:55"},
{"id":"31","question":"Who is the first prophet quoted in the Gospel of Mark?","optn1":"Jeremiah","optn2":"Daniel","optn3":"Isaiah","optn4":"Hosea","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:57:48","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:57:48"},
{"id":"32","question":"In whose house did Jesus dine with publicans and sinners?","optn1":"Peter","optn2":"John","optn3":"Levi","optn4":"Judas","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 02:59:23","updated_at":"2022-10-19 02:59:23"},
{"id":"33","question":"Where was Jesus when he taught the parable of the sower?","optn1":"In a boat","optn2":"On a mountain","optn3":"In Temple","optn4":"Sprawling ground ","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:29:09","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:29:09"},
{"id":"34","question":"Name of the official of Synagogue whose daughter Jesus healed","optn1":"Jairus","optn2":"Josephine","optn3":"James","optn4":"Josiah","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:32:58","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:32:58"},
{"id":"35","question":"During the transfiguration, who appeared to Jesus and the three disciples?","optn1":"Adam and Noah","optn2":"Abraham and David","optn3":"Enoch and Solomon","optn4":"Moses and Elijah","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:34:59","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:34:59"},
{"id":"36","question":"What did the Sadducees not believe in or practice?","optn1":"Resurrection","optn2":"Sacrifices","optn3":"The Law","optn4":"God","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:36:42","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:36:42"},
{"id":"37","question":"After the last supper, what did Jesus and his disciples do before going to the Mount of Olives?","optn1":"Read the prophecy of Daniel","optn2":"Changed their shoes","optn3":"Sung a hymn","optn4":"Offered a sacrifice","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:39:56","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:39:56"},
{"id":"38","question":"Who went to the tomb of Jesus with Mary Magdalene and Mary (mother of James) to anoint Jesus?","optn1":"Salome","optn2":"Joanna","optn3":"Martha","optn4":"Elizabeth","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:42:02","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:42:02"},
{"id":"39","question":"Who was David's father?","optn1":"Abraham","optn2":"Jesse","optn3":"Mordecai","optn4":"Boyaz","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:45:49","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:45:49"},
{"id":"40","question":"Which prophet anointed David as king?","optn1":"Elijah","optn2":"Isaiah","optn3":"Samuel","optn4":"Nathan","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:46:57","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:46:57"},
{"id":"41","question":"Which musical instrument did David play for Saul?","optn1":"Harp","optn2":"Flute","optn3":"Dulcimer","optn4":"Harpsichord","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:48:41","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:48:41"},
{"id":"42","question":"Who was David's great friend?","optn1":"Naboth","optn2":"Abner","optn3":"Jonathan","optn4":"Daniel","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:50:01","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:50:01"},
{"id":"43","question":"How long did David reign?","optn1":"40 years","optn2":"47 years","optn3":"49 years","optn4":"50 years","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:51:24","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:51:24"},
{"id":"44","question":"Which of David's sons rebelled against him and stole the hearts of Israel","optn1":"Solomon","optn2":"Amnon","optn3":"Absalom","optn4":"Adonijah","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:52:47","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:52:47"},
{"id":"45","question":"What phrase did God apply to David?","optn1":"A man after my own heart","optn2":"The friend of God","optn3":"My beloved son","optn4":"My favoured servant","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:56:01","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:56:01"},
{"id":"46","question":"Where was David born?","optn1":"Jerusalem","optn2":"Bethel","optn3":"Bethlehem","optn4":"Beersheba","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:57:43","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:57:43"},
{"id":"47","question":"Why wasn't David allowed to build God's house?","optn1":"Because of his sin with Bathsheba","optn2":"Because he was a man of war","optn3":"Because he wasn't a builder","optn4":"Because he didn't have enough money","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 03:59:14","updated_at":"2022-10-19 03:59:14"},
{"id":"48","question":"How old was David when he died?","optn1":"108","optn2":"95","optn3":"82","optn4":"70","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 05:17:05","updated_at":"2022-10-19 05:17:05"},
{"id":"49","question":"What was the name of Joshua's father?","optn1":"Carmi","optn2":"Nun","optn3":"Othniel","optn4":"Eleazar","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-19 05:19:14","updated_at":"2022-10-19 05:19:14"},
{"id":"50","question":"What was the name of the woman who hid the spies Joshua sent?","optn1":"Rachel","optn2":"Ruth","optn3":"Rahab","optn4":"Rebekah","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 05:21:53","updated_at":"2022-10-19 05:21:53"},
{"id":"51","question":"What natural phenomenon helped Joshua defeat the Amorites?","optn1":"Sandstorm","optn2":"Flood","optn3":"Earthquake","optn4":"Hailstones","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-19 05:30:25","updated_at":"2022-10-19 05:30:25"},
{"id":"52","question":"What was the only tribe not to receive an inheritance?","optn1":"Reuben","optn2":"Issachar","optn3":"Levi","optn4":"Manasseh","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-19 05:34:10","updated_at":"2022-10-19 05:34:10"},
{"id":"53","question":"How many priests were chosen to carry the rams' horns as they marched round Jericho?","optn1":"3","optn2":"7","optn3":"14","optn4":"70","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-24 07:59:33","updated_at":"2022-10-24 07:59:33"},
{"id":"54","question":"Which king of Israel did Elijah warn about an imminent drought?","optn1":"Jehu","optn2":"Omri","optn3":"Ahab","optn4":"Ahaziah","ans":"3","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:04:31","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:04:31"},
{"id":"55","question":"How many times did Elijah stretch himself over the widow's dead son before he was revived?","optn1":"3","optn2":"4","optn3":"2","optn4":"5","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:05:55","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:05:55"},
{"id":"56","question":"Why did Elijah choose 12 stones to build his altar?","optn1":"One for each gate of the temple","optn2":"That's all he could find","optn3":"The number of years Ahab had reigned","optn4":"One for each tribe of Israel","ans":"4","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:12:06","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:12:06"},
{"id":"57","question":"Thy word is a lamp unto my feet, and a light unto my path - what is bible reference","optn1":"Psalms 119:130","optn2":"Psalms 119:105","optn3":"Psalms 89:12","optn4":"Psalms 119:108","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:16:50","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:16:50"},
{"id":"58","question":"Jesus saith unto him, I am the way, the truth, and the life: no man cometh unto the Father, but by me.  Reference ","optn1":"John 14:9","optn2":"Mathew 14:6","optn3":"John 14:6","optn4":"Mark 13:8","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:23:13","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:23:13"},
{"id":"59","question":"For all have sinned, and come short of the glory of God; Reference ?","optn1":"Romans 3:23","optn2":"Romans 12:23","optn3":"Romans 1:21","optn4":"Romans 10:23","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:25:34","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:25:34"},
{"id":"60","question":"The elderly widowed prophetess in Jerusalem, who saw Jesus as a baby was?","optn1":"Anna","optn2":"Rachel","optn3":"Tabitha","optn4":"Salome","ans":"1","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:28:43","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:28:43"},
{"id":"61","question":"Who said to Mary, \"Blessed are you among women, and blessed is the fruit of your womb!\"?","optn1":"Joseph","optn2":"Elisabeth","optn3":"Zechariah","optn4":"Simeon","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:30:38","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:30:38"},
{"id":"62","question":"What does the name \"Matthew\" mean?","optn1":"The Lord is here","optn2":"Gift of the Lord","optn3":"Treasures of the Lord","optn4":"The Lord is merciful","ans":"2","created_at":"2022-10-24 08:32:37","updated_at":"2022-10-24 08:32:37"}
]
}
]
